live.
Like I said, welcome brothers and
sisters to another Wednesday question
and answer where we open up with the ten
commandments that God commanded the
whole world to keep. Brother Tanzel, and
God spake all these words, saying, I am
the Lord thy God, which brought thee out
of the land of Egypt, out of the house
of bondage. Thou shall have no other
gods before me. Thou shalt not make unto
thee any graven image, or any likeness
of anything that is in heaven above, or
that is in the earth beneath, or that is
in the water under the earth. Thou shall
not bow down thyself to them, nor serve
them. For I the Lord thy God am a
jealous God, visiting the iniquities of
the fathers upon the children, unto the
third and fourth generation of them that
hate me, and showing mercy unto thousand
them that love me, and keep my
commandments.
Thou shalt not take the name of the Lord
thy God in vain. For the Lord will not
hold him guiltless that take up his name
in vain. Remember the Sabbath day to
keep it holy. Six days shall thou labor
and do all thy work, but the seventh day
he is the Sabbath of the Lord thy God.
In it thou shall not do any work. Thou
nor thy son, nor thy daughter, thy man's
servant, nor thy maid servant, nor thy
cattle, nor thy stranger that is within
thy gates. For on six days the Lord made
heaven and earth, the sea, and all that
in their midst, and rested the seventh
day. Wherefore the Lord blessed the
Sabbath day, and hallowed it. Honor thy
father and thy mother, that thy days may
be long upon the land which the Lord thy
God giveth thee. Thou shall not kill,
thou shall not commit adultery, thou
shall not steal. Thou sh bear false
witness against thy neighbor. Thou shall
not cover thy neighbor's house. Thou
shalt not cover thy neighbor's wife, nor
his man's servant, nor his maid servant,
nor his ox, nor his ass, nor anything
that is thy neighbors. We read Exodus
21-17. And may the Lord have a blessing
to the reading of his words. In Jesus
name we pray. Amen.
Amen.
So here on question and answer, you can
ask us a question and we'll answer it
according to the King James Bible. And
if we cannot find the answer, we will
seek further counsel to bring you an
answer at a later time. The questions we
will not answer are the vague as well as
the long scripture questions.
So we ask that you please keep your
questions to a two question maximum. We
are here only to spread the true gospel
of Jesus. So please be as direct as
possible with your questions so we can
be as direct as possible with our
answers out of the King James Bible. No
other Bibles or books will be
acknowledged on this program. Also, keep
in mind this is a live stream and you
may begin to send in your questions that
pertain to everlasting life. Let me
introduce you to the family that's on
the panel this evening. Brother Jerome,
rest in peace. Brother Julius, good
evening everybody. Brother Dre, good
evening. Brother Tanzel, good evening.
Sister Deborah, good evening. And we
have Sister Casey as well as a guest
caller with us. And I'm brother Cornell.
What is our first question of the
evening? Yes, there are several held
over questions that will be answered
first before getting into tonight's Q&A.
Uh so, Henga J. Israel says in
Deuteronomy 23:E3
and Nehemiah 13 verse1
he says I need more understanding on
this law if so how was Ruth able to be
married to Boaz also h how does the law
relate to today's time
all right being married to for brother
Julius. What you got? Let's go there and
read
Deuteronomy 23. You don't have to go to
Nehemiah because it says the exact same
thing. Deuteronomy 23, brother Tanzel.
And this time we going to start at verse
one
because the Lord had restrictions on uh
for certain reasons and on certain
people. Go ahead. Let's read quick. Go
ahead. He that is wounded in the stones
or have his private member cut off shall
not enter into the congregation of the
Lord.
A bas
Go ahead, bro. A basel should not enter
into the congreg congregation of the
Lord. Even to his 10th generation shall
he not enter into the congregation of
the Lord. Uhhuh. An Ammonite or
Moabitete shall not enter into the
congregation of the Lord. Even to their
tenth generation shall they not enter
into the congregation of the Lord
forever. Now Ammon and Moab was Lot's
children and they lay with their father
and that's how they came about. They lay
with their father Lot after the
destruction of Sodom and Gomorrah and
that's how they came about. Now, they're
not trying to get into the priesthood or
into that uh they're
they're not trying to get into the
priesthood, but the Lord had restriction
for his reasons. Let's go to Ruth the
first chapter. Ruth was a Moabitis. He
was of of the people of Moab.
The Ammonites and the Moabites served
different gods.
And there was a law in Israel that if a
a wife became a widow and they had no
children and the husband and they had no
children and the husband died, then the
next of kin the next of kin could uh
redeem her and
lay with the woman and keep the deceased
seed alive.
Ruth was a Moabitis. Let's go to Ruth uh
1 and read 15-1 17 quickly.
And she said, "Behold, thy sister-in-law
is gone back unto her people and unto
her gods. Return thou after that
sister-in-law." Now, in verse 14, Ruth
uh and her sister Orpa were
daughter-in-laws to Naomi. Okay?
But they were of the tribe of Moab. So
Naomi sent them back to their lands. Or
went back to her gods, but Ruth stayed
with uh read verse 16. And Ruth said,
"Entreat me not to leave thee, or to
return from following after thee. For
with for thou goest, I will go. And
where thou lodest, I will lodge. And thy
people shall be my people, and thy God
my God." right there. She accepted the
God of Israel. She accepted Naomi's God,
which was the God of Israel. She forsook
the pagan gods that they were came up
and serving. And she latched on to the
God of Israel. And she told Naomi,
"I'mma stay with you no matter what."
Read the whole story on your own. I'mma
stay with you no matter what. Your God
going to be my God, and my God shall be
your God. Ruth chapter 2, 1 verse 11.
Look what Boaz said about Ruth. Go
ahead. And Boaz answered and said unto
her, "I have fully been showed me all
that thou has done." That over again,
brother. And Boaz answered and said unto
her, "It have fully been shown me.
It has fully been shown thee. Shown to
me." Go ahead.
all thou hast done unto thy
mother-in-law since the death of thy
husband, and how thou hast left thy
father, and thy mother, and the land of
thy neativity, and are come unto a
people which thou kneest not here to
for. So now Boaz recognized, and now
let's go to our final verse, our final
chapter, Ruth 3 and verse
11.
Ruth 3 and verse 11. When you get it,
read it. And now, my daughter, fear not.
I will do to thee all that thou
requires. For all the city of my people
do know that thou art a virtuous woman.
And verse 13, go ahead. Terry this
night, and it shall be in the morning,
that if he will perform unto thee the
part of a kinsman, the part of a
kinsman, that's the law.
I'm going go ahead.
Well, let him do the kinsman's part. But
if he will not do the part of a kinsman
to thee, then will I do the part of a
kinsman to thee as
now the last scripture Ruth 4 and verse
when you get it? Read it. So Boaz took
Ruth and she was his wife. And when he
went in into her, the Lord gave her
conception, and she bareed a son. So how
did Boaz take Ruth the wife? She latched
on to the God of Israel, kept his
commandments, a virtuous woman, and he
found favor in her eyes, and he redeemed
her as a relative because her husband
was dead. And so he played that law was
if you didn't have no children, if the
man didn't have no children, the next
kinman could redeem her and take her to
be his wife. Your God going to be my
God. Your people going to be my people.
And she proved that and was a virtuous
woman. And he married her, right? That's
all I got. That's how she became. And as
for does that apply today? It does not
apply today. That would be called
incest. That's all I got. Cornell.
All right. Thank you for that. Hope that
answered your question. As Ruth made a
good move by serving the God of Israel
and she became David's grandmother.
Yep. All right. We hope that answered
your question as we move on to our next
one. Moving on. Be alert as in Matthew
25 verse 34 and Revelations 21:16.
Did the Lord have a set number elected
for adoption into the God's family from
the beginning of creation?
Is this why the father's kingdom has a
set dimension?
All right, this question starts off in
Matthew 25 and 34 and the guest caller
will take it from there.
Okay, let's go let's go into Matthews 25
and read verse 34.
Okay.
And then shall the king say unto them,
be on his right hand, come ye the bless
of my father, inherit the kingdom
prepared for you from the foundation of
the world.
Now this is when uh Jesus come.
If you start at the top at at verse 31
to let you know this is uh uh uh what
Jesus when he came
and uh uh all the nations going to have
to pass before in fact just back up and
and start at verse 31. We're going to
read quickly.
And when the Son of Man shall come in
his glory, and all the holy angels with
him, then shall he sit upon the throne
of his glory.
And before him shall be gathered all
nations, and he shall separate them one
from another, as a sheep divide of his
sheep from the goats. And he shall set
the sheep on his right hand, and the
goats on the left. Then shall the king
say unto them,
Now read the other. Go ahead.
Then shall the king say unto them on his
right hand, come ye blessed of my father
and
inherit the kingdom prepared for you
from the foundation of the world.
Now that's the father's kingdom,
but that started when Jesus come. So let
let's we're going to do a quick run on
on some scriptures and work up to that.
So that's when Jesus came. But let's go
to Zechariah the 9th chapter and read
verses 9 and 10.
Zechariah 9.
Uhhuh.
9 and 10.
Rejoice greatly, O daughter of Zion.
Shout, O daughter of Jerusalem. Behold,
thy kingdom cometh unto thee. He is
just, and having salvation lowly, and
riding upon the ass, and upon a coat,
the fold up of an ass.
And I will cut off the chariot from
Ephraim, and the horse from Jerusalem.
And the bow shall be cut off, and he
shall speak peace unto the heathens, and
his dominion shall be from sea even to
sea, and from the river even to the ends
of the earth.
Now, this let this let us know right
there. When Jesus come, he is not going
to just run Jerusalem. He is going to
rule this entire planet. Okay?
Let's look how long he's going going
he's going to rule it. Go to Revelation
20th chapter, read verse 4 and six. 4 to
6.
And I saw thrones, and they sat upon
them, and judgment was given unto them.
And I saw the souls of them that were
beheaded for the witness of Jesus and
for the word of God, and which have not
worshiped the beast, neither his image,
neither have received his mark upon
their forehead or in their hands. And
they lived and reigned with Christ a
thousand years. But the rest of the dead
not again until the thousand years were
finished. This is the first
resurrection.
But blessed holy is he that hath part in
the first resurrection. on such the
second death have no power. But they
shall be priests of God and of Christ
and shall reign with him a thousand
years.
Now that let you know that he going to
rule with Jesus a thousand years. Now we
going to look at uh uh uh we going to
bring down now
he and see what happened at the end of
the thousand years.
Go to 1 Corinthians 15th chapter. Read
verses 24 and 26 and skip down and read
verse 28.
Then cometh the end when he shall
deliver up the kingdom to God even the
father when he shall have put down all
and all authority and power.
Now that's that's come that then come at
the end of Jesus
thousand year rule. That's after he done
then he going to deliver up the kingdom
to the father and then he going to put
down all pick it up right there. Put
down all enemies. Go ahead.
Put down all rule and all authority and
power for he must reign till he have put
all enemies under his feet. The last
enemy that shall be destroyed is death.
Skip down to verse 28 and read it. And
when all things shall be subdued unto
him, then shall the son also himself be
subject unto him that put all things
unto him, that God may be all in all.
So now Jesus going to run this entire
earth for a thousand years. He going to
terminate death, put out all enemies and
all rule. Now once he do that, he is
going to turn it over to the father.
Now
let's look at the father coming down
from heaven. Revelation 21
and we're going to start reading at
verse we're going to read verse two and
three first.
And I, John, saw the holy city, New
Jerusalem, coming down from God out of
heaven, prepared as a bride adorned for
her husband. And I heard a great voice
out of heaven, saying, "Behold, the
tabernacle of God is with men, and he
will dwell with them, and they shall be
his people, and God himself shall be
with them, and be their God."
So now, the holy city, New Jerusalem. It
didn't say a holy earth, did it?
Holy city. So that's what's coming down.
Skip down to verse 16 and read it.
And the city lith four square, and the
length is as large as the breath. And he
measured the city with the reed 12,000
furongs. The length and the breath and
the height of it are equal.
Now, that was New Jerusalem, the holy
city. That was not the whole earth.
That was just one city. Now, skip now to
verse 23. Read verse 23 and 24.
And the city had no need of the sun,
neither neither of the moon to shine in
it, for the glory of God did lighten it,
and the Lamb is the light thereof. and
the nations of them which are saved
shall walk in the light of it. And the
kings of the earth do bring their glory
and honor into it.
Now this this is what most people don't
understand. The Lord has set this earth
up like he wanted. He got nations like
he wanted.
So once Jesus ruled this earth for a
thousand years because they already say
in other scripture, everybody going to
return turn to their own people and and
everybody's going to flee to their own
country. Right? So you going to have
nations just like you have now.
And the only difference is they all
going to be holy. They all going to be
immortal. And they all going to be God.
But they all not going to be crammed in
New Jerusalem because New Jerusalem is
just one one city out of many nations
with many cities.
Even as New Jerusalem, it didn't even
name all of the uh uh uh cities that was
in Israel.
So no, that dimension is only given of
New Jerusalem. That is where God and
Jesus is going to dwell. And I'm pretty
sure you going to have some people dwell
in there, citizens of Jerusalem, but
they going to be immortals.
So now this dimension defines a city.
But the Lord is coming down. He's coming
down to the earth where there are whole
lot of nations and there a whole lot of
cities. That's why it said and the
nations that are saved going to walk in
the light of that city and the kings
that are going to bring their glory unto
it. But they're not all going to be
crammed in it. They all going to be in
their own nation.
And just remember, New Jerusalem is one
city of many cities that's going to be
on this earth. It just going to be a
different type being. That's all I have
to say. All right. I hope that answered
your question as we move on to our next
one. Jennifer Love says, "Why the KJV
Bible? What scriptures can be given when
people say we are saved by grace and not
the commandments?
Guess caller.
The first thing is we need use the King
James version because this is
commissioned
by God and is the most comprehensive
version put out and it can be backed up
with history. That's the first thing.
But as far as people saying that they we
live by grace, people don't understand
uh uh uh what grace is.
And that don't mean because you grace,
you're under grace, you can't sin. Let's
go into Romans the 6th chapter.
We're going to read verses 14- 16 first.
Then we're going to skip
Romans 6 and verse 14.
For sin shall not have dominion over
you. For ye not under the law, but under
grace.
But what then? Shall we sin because we
not under the law, but under grace? God
forbid. But know ye not that to whom ye
yield yourself servants to obey, his
servants ye are to whom ye obey, whether
of sin unto death or of obedience unto
righteousness.
Now grace is a free free gift. When Adam
and Eve sin in the garden that put us
under death sentence, Jesus came and
lifted the death sentence.
But before that we had uh that's why he
said that shall we stand because we
under grace God from dead. Don't you
know whoever you yield your members to
that's who sin what you are grace under
life or either sin under death. Get down
because because what what is the wages
of skin? Sin. Read verse 23.
For the wages of sin is death but the
gift of God is eternal life through
Jesus Christ our Lord.
The people saying that you you're under
grace, you don't have to keep no law.
They don't understand
that law that you ain't under anymore is
the law of animal sacrifice. Let's go to
Hebrews the 10th chapter.
Read verse one.
Then we're going to skip to verse four
and five. Verse one first.
For the law having a shadow of good
things to come and not the very image of
the things can never with those
sacrifices which they offer year by year
continually make the convers there unto
perfect.
Now see this law is the law of animal
sacrifice. Most of the world don't even
know about that because they don't even
read the old testament. But this law
look uh could never make the come there
perfect through
animal sacrifice. Why? Get down and read
verse four and five.
For it is not possible that the blood of
bulls and of goats should take away
sins.
Uhhuh. But when he cometh into the
world, he says, "Sacrifice and offering
thou wouldest not, but a body has thou
prepared me."
Now he let you know that look, you
couldn't become perfect because
sacrificing an offering wouldn't remove
sin. So Jesus say he needed a body
because this man had to have a sin
offering. So what did Jesus what did why
didn't Jesus need that body? Skip down
to verse 10 and uh uh verse 10 and read
it.
By the which will we are sanctified
through the offering of the body of
Jesus Christ once for all.
So now Jesus came and he was offered one
for one and for all that terminated
animal sacrifice. Read verse 14.
For by one offering he have perfected
forever them that are sanctified.
Now by one offering do now what happened
to that law of animal sacrifice? Skip
down to verse 18 and read it.
Now where we mention of these is there
is no more offering for sin.
So that is the law that you're not under
anymore. The law of animal sacrifice. It
could not remove sin any way.
who as long as you was killing animals
and before Jesus came, you was uh uh uh
you was subject to sin and die like you
still are. So, you have to keep the law.
But let's go into Romans the 5th chapter
and we're going to read verse 12
and then we're going to skip
Romans 5 and 12.
Romans 5 and 12. Yeah, I'm sorry. That's
what I mean. 5 and 12. Go ahead.
Wherefore, as by one man sin enter into
the world, and death by sin, and so
death passed upon all men, for that all
have sinned.
Okay. And that one man was Adam. Skip
down to verse 17 and read it. For if by
one man offense,
Yeah. 17, go ahead.
For if by one man's offense death
reigned by one, then much more they
which receive abundance of grace and of
the gift of righteousness shall reign in
life by one Jesus Christ.
Keep reading to 21. Go ahead. Therefore,
as by the offense of one judgment came
upon all men to condemnation, even so by
the righteousness of one, the free gift
came upon all men unto justification of
life. For as by one man's disobedience,
many were made sinners, so by the
obedience of one shall many be made
righteous.
Moreover,
who?
Moreover, the law entered
verse 20. Go ahead.
Moreover, the law entered that the
office might abound. But where sin
abound, grace did much more abound. That
as sin have reigned unto death, even so
might grace reign through righteousness
unto eternal life by Jesus Christ our
Lord.
Now, so Jesus brought the free gift, but
then you have to believe in Jesus and
and you have to do what he say. Now go
to Romans the 5th chapter now and read 1
and two.
5 1 and two. Back up and read verse one
Therefore, being justified by faith, we
have peace with God through our Lord
Jesus Christ, by whom also we have
access by faith unto his grace, wherein
we stand. Now,
did you let's finish it. See, this is
what people overlook.
Read it again one and two before I
comment.
Therefore, being justified by faith, we
have peace with God through our Lord
Jesus Christ. by whom also we have
access by faith into it into this grace
wherein we stand and rejoice in hope of
the glory of God.
Now, in order for you to get come under
this grace, you have to have some faith,
right? If you don't believe in him, then
you're not going to do what he's saying.
Then you don't have no faith. In order
for you to enter into this grace, you
have to have faith. and go to Ephesians
2, read 4:5.
Ephesians 2, 4 and 5. Because I want you
to understand that uh this grace is
there. But in order for you to take
advantage of this grace, you have to
have faith in the Lord. And the Lord
tell you to told you to obey his voice.
And one of the things he said, you got
to keep the commandments. Go ahead and
read four and five.
Look not every man on his own things,
but every man also on the things of
other. But let this mind be in you which
was also in Christ Jesus.
I'm sorry.
Ephesians 4 and 5. Ephesians chapter 2
verses four and five.
But God, who is rich in mercy, for his
great love wherewith he loved us, even
when we were dead in sins, have
quickened us together with Christ, by
grace ye are saved.
Okay? So, you're saved by grace because
you have to believe. But you have to
have some belief. Skip down to verse
eight and read it.
For by grace are ye saved through faith,
and that not of yourselves. It is the
gift of God.
Now, pay attention. By grace are you
saved through
faith.
So, you got to believe. So, if you're a
believer, let's see what's going to
happen concerning the law. Now, let's go
uh uh in Romans 3 is going to be the
last one. Romans 3 23 and 24 first. Go
ahead.
Yes. For all have sinned and come short
of the glory of God,
being justified freely by his grace
through the redemption that is in Christ
Jesus
whom God have sent.
Go ahead.
Was it 23 to 25?
24.
Okay, that was it.
Okay. So now we all have of of sin. So
we needed Jesus to come and die for our
sin and give us this free gift. But in
order for us to get this free gift, we
got to have faith. In other words, you
got to do what the Lord say. Now skip
down and read verse 26 through 28.
to declare to declare I say at this time
his righteousness that he might be just
and the justifier of him which believe
in Jesus. But where is boasting then? It
is excluded by what law of works? Nay,
but by the law of faith. So therefore we
conclude that a man is justified by
faith without the deeds of the law.
Now, so now in order for you to get this
grace, you have to have faith. And uh
man is justified by grace by faith
without the deeds of the law. And ain't
talking about animal sacrifice. It's
talking about it's not talking about the
royal law. That's talking about animal
sacrifice. So now if you are just by
justified by faith,
what will you do concerning the royal
law? Skip down and read verse 31.
Do we then make void the law through
faith? God forbid. Yay. We establish the
law. That's right. Do not
do not. Do we make void the law through
faith? God forbid. No, we establish the
law. So, how do you establish the law?
By keeping it. Yes.
The blood of Jesus terminated the law of
animal sacrifice
and gave you a free gift. But if you
want to uh uh uh profit from that free
gift, you got to have faith. And if you
got to have faith and your faith, you
are going to establish the law. And you
do that by keeping the law. That's the
royal law, the commandments.
One law was broken, the commandment, God
added animal sacrifice, but the animal
sacrifice couldn't help. But then Jesus
came and died for you. And you got a
free gift, which is grace. But in order
for you to get that grace, you got to
have faith. And if you have faith, you
got to establish the law. You got to
keep the commandments. That's all I have
to say. All right. Hope that answers
your question as we move on to our next
one. Moving on. She also says, "Wasn't
Saul the first king of Israel?"
And she has a few more questions. Was
the tribe of Benjamin the first
Solomonites?
And in Genesis 22 verse one, she says,
"I thought that God would not tempt us."
Explain.
All right, Jennifer, we ask that you
please keep your questions to two
and we're gonna ask brother Jerome to be
kind and shed some light on that.
Um, on that first question, um,
Saul, uh, he was the first king of
Israel,
um, who was flesh and blood.
Okay. The actual first king of Israel
was the God of Israel
who was under the name Jehovah at the
time. Okay, the I am. All right. So now
let's go to 1 Samuel
8th chapter
and we going to read verse 5-7 and then
we going to hit that ninth chapter after
that.
You get it? Go ahead and read 1 Samuel 8
verse 5-7.
and said unto him, "Behold, thou our
old, and thy sons walk not in thy ways.
Now make us a king to judge us like all
the nations."
But the thing displeased Samuel when
they said, "Give us a king to judge us."
And Samuel prayed unto the Lord. And the
Lord said unto Samuel, "But heark unto
the voice of the people in all that they
say unto thee, for they have not
rejected thee, but they have rejected
me, that I should not reign over them."
God, the Lord God of Israel, should not
reign over them. He was their king.
Okay? Then they wanted a king of flesh
and blood. And the Lord said, "I'mma
give you one."
Okay? And Samuel was the first one
given. Uh uh Saul was the first one
given. Okay. So now go to the ninth
chapter and read verse 15 and 16.
Now the Lord
go ahead. Now the Lord had told Samuel
in his ear a day before Saul came,
saying, "Tomorrow about this time, I
will send thee a man out of the land of
Benjamin, and thou shalt anoint him to
be captain over my people Israel, that
he may save my people out of the hands
of the Philistines, for I have looked
upon my people, because their cry is
come unto me."
Okay. Now, quickly go to the 15th
chapter. Read verse 20. Then we going to
skip.
And Saul said unto Samuel, "Yeah, I have
obeyed the voice of the Lord, and have
done the way which the Lord sent me, and
have brought Aad and the king of Amel."
That's good. Skip down to verse 22 and
23. Amalecch and have utterly destroyed
the Amalachites. And Samuel said, "Have
the Lord as great delight in the burnt
offerings and sacrifices, as is obeying
the voice of the Lord? Behold, obey is
better than sacrifice,
and to hearken than the fat of ram."
Uhhuh. For rebellion is as the sin of
witchcraft, and stubbornness is as
iniquity and idolatry. Because thou hast
reject the word of the Lord, he hath
also reject thee from being king. And
that's what he talking about to rule
over my people. He talking about king.
So Saul was king
of flesh and blood, the first one. Okay.
So now your second question,
uh,
was Benjamin the first Sodomite? No.
Okay. Because before the uh Israelites
were even in existence, you had the
people of Sodom, right? Okay. And they
were sodomites in their land long before
the Israelites even existed. Okay? So,
uh and when you get the time, go to
Jude. We not gonna go there, but go to
Jude in the New Testament and read verse
seven because a but one chapter. Now, in
your third question,
uh, let's go to Genesis 22:1.
When you get it, go ahead and read.
And it came to pass after these things
that God did tempt Abraham and said unto
him, Abraham, and he said, behold, here
my here I am.
And he said, take now thy son, thy only
son. Yeah. 22 and1.
Okay. So now you have to understand
words have more than one definition.
Tempt in this case mean he tried
Abraham. And then there's another place
we going to go to to establish that the
Lord don't tip tempt you. And I'm going
to show you what he mean by he don't
tempt you. Okay. So let's go to James
chapter one.
And we going to read verse 13
and 14.
When you get it, go ahead and read. Let
no man say when he is tempted, I am
tempted of God. For God cannot be
tempted with evil, neither tempted he
any man. He ain't tempting you with no
evil. Okay? But if he tempt you, he
trying you. Because that's the
definition you apply with the word temp
because he don't tempt nobody,
especially with no evil. Hey, did you
finish that?
Yeah. But every man is tempted when he
is drawn away of his own lust and
enticed. Every man is tempted when he is
drawn away of his own lust. The Lord
ain't tempting you. Right. Okay. That's
all I got on you.
All right. Thank you for that, brother.
As we move on to our next question,
moving on. Humility Israel asks, "Is
there a scripture that clearly states we
cannot eat with others that believe in a
different doctrine?"
All right, Julius,
answer is no. Let me show you what the
book says.
Let's go to 1 Corinthians chapter 5.
Is there a scripture that clearly states
we cannot eat with others that believe
in a different doctrine? That's not
written nowhere in the Bible.
Let's let's show you what is written in
the Bible. First Corinthians chapter 5,
we're going to read verse 9 and we going
to read verse 11.
When you get it, Tenzel, go ahead. I
wrote unto you and an epistol, not to
accompany with fornicators, not to not
to company with people of a different
religion.
Fornicators. Verse 11, but now I have
written unto you, not to keep company,
if any man that is called a brother, be
a fornicator, fornicator
or a covetous. Uhhuh. Or or an idoltor.
or a or a [__] Somebody that's always
insulting somebody with harsh language.
Go ahead. Or drunker. Uhhuh. Or an
extortioner. Uhhuh. With such a one. No.
Not to eat. Those are the people that
you don't eat with.
Had nothing to do with their religion.
Has something to do with their
behaviors.
So therefore, that's what this is
actually saying. Because what if
somebody says I want to come out of u
what I'm doing in my uh out of my uh
religion or whatever my faith and I want
to come to the to the Israel of God. Can
we talk about it, brother Julius? I buy
you I buy you lunch. I buy you dinner.
I got to talk to that person.
So that's my answer for that one.
Brother Cornell,
right? Thank you for that, brother. as
we move on to our next question with a
time check. Yes, the time is 8:13.
Jennifer Love asks in Revelation 9
verse4, "What is the seal of God?" Let's
go to Revelation 9 and4 and see what it
says about that seal of God and uh guess
call and take it from there.
Well, she gave the wrong scripture. is
Revelation
7 and 4.
So go there. Revelation 7 and 4 and read
verse four.
And I heard the number of them which
were sealed and they were sealed and 140
and4,000 of all the tribes of the
children of Israel.
Now what they saying is what is the seal
of God?
that he's sealed there in Revelation.
We don't know.
That's all I have to say. All right,
we're going to move on to our next
question. Next question. She also says,
"I'm curious. Is it necessary that
people that know the truth to always
beat others over the head with the word?
Isn't it better to know the time and
place to avoid turning people away?
Brother Dre, what you say? So, you asked
two questions then. That is,
is it necessary to that people that know
the truth beat others over the head with
the word?
Is it necessary? No, not necessarily.
But is there a time and a place for
that? Sure, I'm sure it is, but not all
the time. Let's go to uh Proverbs
27.
Question I have for you is, if you love
somebody, do you tell them
when they are headed down the wrong
road? Do you beat them over the head?
No. But do you tell them? Proverbs 27,
read verses five and six.
Go ahead, brother. Open rebuke is better
than secret love.
People are the wounds of a friend, but
the kisses of an enemy are deceitful. Oh
yeah. Hey, open rebuke is love.
Sometimes people only can hear open
rebuke and it's better than not saying
nothing but beating them over the head.
That's a whole another thing. Is there a
time and a place? Let's go to uh
Ecclesiastics
Ecclesiastes 3 right quick. Ecclesiastes
3. We going to read verse one and skip.
Go ahead, brother, when you get it.
Okay. Ecclesiastes 3 and 6. Three and
verse one.
To everything there is a seed and a time
to every purpose under heaven.
Read verse seven. Go ahead. A time to
rent and a time to sow. A time to keep
silence and a time to speak. Yeah,
there's a time to speak and a time to
keep silence. Now, let's go over to
Proverbs
15. Proverbs 15 and 23.
So, it kind of depends. Proverbs 15. Not
to beat somebody over the head-au
because you don't want to turn them away
from the truth. Right. Proverbs 15 verse
23. Go ahead, brother.
A man have joy by the answers of his
mouth and a word spoken in due season,
how good is he. Yeah. So there is a time
and a season and a time and a place for
everything. And a word spoken in due
season is a good word. One last place.
Proverbs 18 and 19. Proverbs 18 and 19.
When you get it, go ahead, brother.
A brother offended is harder to be
warned than a strong city. And their
contentions are like the bars of a
castle. Yeah. You know, Proverbs 15 tell
you a soft answer turn away wrath, but
grievous words stir up anger. But
there's a season. Even the Lord told
Ezekiel, he said, as a watchman, you got
to tell the people whether they heal or
whether they forbear. But do you beat
them over the head? No.
You don't. I hope that helps.
All right. Thank you for that, brother.
As we move on to our next question.
Moving on. Bryer Ben asked for you to
explain the parable that the Lord God
spoke in Isaiah 28
23-
29.
What did he mean?
the parable in Isaiah 28
and verse 23.
Tanzel, when you get there, I guess
caller would take it from there.
Was it uh 23 all the way to 29?
Yes.
Okay. Go ahead. Give ye ear and hear my
voice. Hearken and hear my speech. Doth
the plow man plow all day to sow? Doth
he open and break the clouds of his of
his ground? When he have made plain the
face thereof,
do he not cast a broth the fitches and
scatter the coming and cast in the
principal wheat and the anointed barley
and the rye in their place. For his God
do instruct him to discretion and do
teach him. For the fitches are not
threshed with a threshing instrument,
neither is a cartwheel turned about upon
the coming. But the fitches are beaten
out with the staff and the coming with
the rod. Bread coin is bruised because
he would not ever be threshing it, nor
break it with the wheel of his cart, nor
bruise it with his horsemen. This also
comes forth from the Lord of hosts which
is wonderful in counsel and excellent in
working
to all all the Lord stand there. Just
like the farmers are instructed
how to raise their crops
come from the Lord. So it is when the
Lord get ready to take down this earth.
Now we going to back back up to the uh
uh 21st chapter. 21st verse rather it is
same chapter and read down to verse 23.
21 and 23
23 rather
for the Lord shall rise up as in Mount
Perism.
and he shall be wroth as in the valley
of Gibian, that he may do his works, his
strange work, and bring to pass his
acts, his strange acts. But now,
therefore, be ye not markers, lest your
hands be made strong. For I have heard
from the Lord God of hosts, a
consumption, even determined upon the
whole earth. Give ye ear, and hear my
voice. Hearken, and hear my speech.
Let me just let you know just like the
Lord instructs you how to farm, he also
you know it come from God. He tells you
how to do your farming. Man wouldn't
have known all of that. All that come
from God. So that same God telling you
just like you are instructed and taught
how to farm,
you are being told through the prophets
of God that he's going to come and he's
going to take down this earth. So hear
what I'm saying.
Everything come from God to the
instruction of farmer and also to
instruct man that God is going to come
and he's going to take down this earth
by force. That's all it's saying. He
using the farmer just like you said just
like he tell you one thing he tell you
everything else right he tell you how to
grow food he tell you also by his
prophet that he going to destroy this
earth
that's all I have to say all right hope
that answered your question next
question next question Brat asks what
did God mean when he said for a sister
that have had no husband, they may
defile themselves. And Ezekiel 44 verse
25 is given, brother Jerome.
Let's go read it.
You get it. Go ahead. Ezekiel 44 and5
25.
Ezekiel 44 and 25.
And they shall come at no dead person to
defile themselves. But for father or for
mother or for son or for daughter or for
brother or for sister that have had no
husband, they may defile themselves.
Okay, this is actually talking about the
uh the priests, the leave of the Levites
uh uh even more uh uh in particular uh
those that come out of Zato. So let's go
read
where it say they these are the one that
he referring to that can be defiled by a
dead body.
And oftentimes people refer to that as
when you, you know, a loved one pass
away, right?
And you go and you deal with the
mourning by even going to a funeral or
so forth or so forth and you make
yourself unclean by their dead body. He
letting the the u the people of Zadok
which is out of Levi he letting them
know everybody mentioned in that 25th
verse he can make himself unclean with
they dead body everybody mentioned in
that verse even with his sister but his
sister got to be unmarried though she
can't have a husband if she got a
husband he can't defile himself with her
dead body by going and and dealing with
her if she pass way, right? But if she
don't have a husband, he can defile
himself with his sister if she pass
away. Okay, so now let's pick it up at
uh that same chapter. Let's pick it up
at verse 14. Read it to the 18. Here we
going to skip.
But I will make them keepers of the
charge of the house for all the service
thereof, and for all that shall be done
therein.
But the priests, the Levites, the sons
of Zad, the the uh that keep the childs
in my sanctuary, when the children of
Israel went astray from me, they shall
come near to me to minister unto me, and
they shall stand before me, to offer
unto me the fat and the blood, said the
Lord God.
Go ahead. and they shall enter into my
sanctuary, and they shall come near to
my table to minister unto me, and they
shall keep my charge. Uhhuh. It shall
come to pass that when they enter in at
the gates of the inner court, they shall
be clothed with linen garments. No wool
shall come upon them, while they
minister in the gates of the inner
court. And with one more verse. And they
shall have linen bonnets upon their upon
their heads and shall have linen
breaches upon their loins. They shall
not g themselves with anything that
causes sweat.
Read that 20 and then we going to skip.
Neither shall they shave their heads,
nor suffer their locks to grow to grow
long. They shall only pole their heads.
Now read that 23- 27 as quickly as you
can. And they shall teach my people the
difference between the holy and profane
and cause them to discern between the
unclean and the clean and their
controversy. They shall stand in
judgment, and they shall judge it
according to my judgment. And they shall
keep my laws and my statutes, and all my
assemblies, and they shall hollow my
Sabbaths, and they shall come at no dead
person to defile themselves. But for
their but for father or for mother or
for son or for daughter or brother or
for sister that have had no husband they
may defile themselves. Man that's that's
good enough. That's that's all I got.
All right. Thank you for that. As we
move on to our next question. Next
question. E. Davies asks, "Is the
incense people burn to make their home
smell good? The same type of incense
mentioned in the Bible?"
I don't, you know, they've been burning
incense for thousands of years. And the
stuff that we got today can't say
whether or not it's the same as what
they used to burn back then. But we can
say that the incense that you do burn,
make sure you don't do it on the Sabbath
day. Right. And that's all I got on
that.
As we continue to move on to our next
question, moving on. Sam Burns says, "My
mistake. I meant is there a correlation
between Isaiah 41 verse 15 and Psalms
verses 6-9.
All right. Isaiah 41-15.
Yes. Go there
and um read that and the guest caller
take it from there. Isaiah 41 and 15.
Isaiah 41 and 15
Behold, I will make thee a new sharp
threshing instrument having teeth. Thou
shalt thrust the mountains and beat them
small, and shall make the hills as
shaft.
Now, now this is this is the Lord
addressing Israel.
And no, this don't correlate with 149th
chapter Psalm. If you had back up, we we
read earlier uh uh when this came in
that this is when the Lord is talking
about particularly about Israel. How is
he going to protect Israel and how he's
going to make Israel a sharp instrument?
In other words, he going to make is
Israel when Israel go to war with
somebody else, he is they going to win
because he is going to be with them.
Yep. But but this uh 149th chapter psalm
is talking about the saints, the people
in the first resurrection.
Two different things all together. So
no, they are not they don't correlate.
But let's show you about uh uh
concerning this. Read that 149th chapter
psalm
and verses 6-9.
Let the high praises of God be in their
mouth, and a two-ed swore in their
hands, to execute vengeance upon the
heathen, and punishment upon the people,
to bind their kings with chains, and
their nobles with feather feathers of
iron, to execute upon them the judgment
written, "This honor have all his
saints." Praise ye the Lord.
He said, "This honor have all his
saints." And this talking about a
worldwide thing. Now, let's show you
because this is and this is going to be
during the thousand years that Jesus
going to rule on this earth.
Let's go in let's go into Isaiah
the uh uh we're going to look at Isaiah
the 41st chapter and show well we
already do doing that but I'm just
letting you know Isaiah the 41st chapter
is speaking particularly Israel and what
Israel is going to do to other people
but now let's go and read 14 we done
read 149th chapter some so we going to
pursue this and show you that this is
talking about his saints and these are
people in the first resurrection we're
going to God first 1 Thessalonians 4th
chapter read verses 13-1 17.
But I would not have you be ignorant,
brethren, concerned them which are
asleep, that ye sorrow not, even as
others which have no hope. For if we
believe that Jesus died and rose again,
even so them also which sleep in Jesus
will God bring with them. But this we
say unto you by the word of the Lord,
that we which are alive, and remain unto
the coming of the Lord shall not pre
prevent them which are asleep.
For the Lord himself shall descend from
heaven with a shout, with the voice of
the archangel, and with the trump of
God, and the dead in Christ shall rise
first.
Then we which are alive shall remain
shall be caught up together with them in
the clouds to meet the Lord in the air.
And so shall we ever be with the Lord.
So now you going to meet the Lord in the
air. So now let's see where you going to
go from there. Go to Zechariah the 14th
chapter, read verses 3 through 5.
Then shall the Lord go forth and fight
against those nations as when he fought
in the day of battle, and his feet shall
stand in that day upon the Mount of
Olive, which is before Jerusalem on the
east. And the Mount of Olive shall
cleave in the midst thereof toward the
east and towards the west. And there
shall be a very great valley, and half
of the mountain shall remove toward the
north, and half of it toward the south,
and ye shall flee to the valley of the
mountains, for the valley of the
mountain shall reach unto Ael. Yeah, ye
shall flee like as ye fled from before
the earthquake in the days of Uzziah,
king of Judah. And the Lord my God shall
come and all the saints with thee.
The Lord's going to come and all the
saints with him. Those are the one that
met him in the air. And where's he going
to be king over? Read verse N. And the
Lord shall be king over all the earth.
In that day shall there be one Lord and
his name one.
Okay. Now let's go into Daniel's the 7th
chapter
and we going to see Jesus coming and and
he going to receive a kingdom and we're
going to see who going to run this
kingdom with him. Daniel 7 and we're
going to read verses 13 and 14. Then
we're going to skip.
I saw in the night vision and behold one
like the son of man came with the clouds
of heaven and came to the ancient of
days and they brought him near before
him.
And there was given him dominion and
glory and a kingdom that all people and
nations and language should serve him.
and his dominion is an everlasting
dominion which shall not pass away and
his kingdom that which shall not be
destroyed.
So now skip down to 18. Let's see who
going to take the kingdom. Verse 18.
But the saints of the most high shall
take the kingdom and possess the kingdom
forever, even forever and ever.
Now where this kingdom going to be
located? Skip down to verse 27 and read
it. And the kingdom and dominion and the
greatness of the kingdom under the whole
heaven shall be given to the people of
the saints of the most high whose
kingdom is a everlasting kingdom and all
dominion shall serve and obey him.
Now this kingdom is going to be on earth
and going to be ran by the people that's
in the first resurrection. The last
place, Revelation 5,
and we're going to read verse 1 and then
we're going to skip and read 6-10.
Revelation 5 verse one, and we're going
to skip and read 6-10.
And I saw in the right hand of him that
sat on the throne, a book written within
and on the backside, sealed with the
seven seals.
Verse six. And I beheld, and lo, in the
midst of the throne, and of the four
beasts, and in the midst of the elders,
stood a lamb, as it had been slain,
having seven horns, and seven eyes,
which are the seven spears of God, sent
forth unto all the earth. And he came
into
Yeah, go ahead.
And he came and took the book out of the
right hand of him that sat upon the
throne. And when he had taken the book
of the four beasts, and four and 20
elders fell down before the lamb, having
every one of them harps and golden vows
full of odors, which are the prayers of
saints.
And they saw that knew so, saying, Thou
are worthy to take the book, and to open
the seals thereof. For thou was slain,
and has redeemed us to God by thy blood,
out of every kindred and tongue, and
people, and nations, and hast made us
unto our God, kings and priests, we
shall reign on the earth.
So now that 169th chapter of Psalms is
telling you that during the millennium
period that the people that are saints,
they going to help Jesus run this thing.
They going to bind kings and they going
to bring punishment upon people that
disobey.
And Isaiah 41st chapter is just talking
about how the Lord is going to work with
Israel. Two different things all
together. One's a mortal one nation and
the other are immortals that are in the
first resurrection that come out of all
nations. That's all I have to say. All
right. Hope that answered your question
as we move on to our next. Yes. Moving
on. Michelle from Louisiana says, "My
special need 12year-old granddaughter
has started her cycle. Do we still do
everything God has instructed us to do
by the book?
Yeah. If you if your question is because
your um granddaughter is 12. Yeah. She
has the the book applies to someone even
if they're grown. So it makes no
difference. But let's go to Proverbs 22.
Proverbs 22. And let's pick it up at
verse
6. Proverbs 22 and 6. Cuz yeah, it's the
it's the same law.
Proverbs 22.
22 and six. When you get there,
train up a child in the way he should
go, and when he is old, he would not
depart from it. Also applies to when she
is old. Train up a a young girl, too.
And hey, the law applies the same
whether it's a young girl or a grown
woman.
And that's all I got.
And we're going to move on to our next
question. Yes. Moving on. Uh Renee
Israel, I want to let her know uh her
question was answered last week. Who are
the 144,000
in Revelation 14 1 and three? So, I'm
moving on. Credit Account uh says,
"Hey, I know we don't know who is who
out of the three tribes brought to
America, but is the head pastor over the
IOG church considered a high priest
since he has to stump sin out in his
congregation?"
All right, guest caller.
The question is no. Go to 110th chapter
Psalm and read verse one
and skip down and read verse four.
Psalms 110
verse one.
The Lord said unto my Lord, sit thou at
my right hand until I make thy enemies
thy foottool.
Okay. Verse four. The Lord has sworn and
he will not repent. Thou art a priest
forever after the order of Mechisedc.
Now that's talking Jesus.
We can go and look at it. Uh but Hebrews
10, but we ain't going there. He's
talking about Jesus the priest forever
after the order of Melia day. Now let's
go into first John and read uh the
second chapter and read verse one.
First John
2 verse one
first John I'm sorry first John uh
chapter one right chapter 2 verse one
okay my little children these things
write I unto you that ye sin not and if
any man sin we have an advocate with the
father Jesus Christ the righteous
Now that Jesus is the high priest, there
is no more flesh and blood high priest.
The last time we had high priest, it was
during the time before Jesus came and
died on the cross. There was a seed of
of of Levi.
So now there ain't no more high priest
on the earth. No matter what men call
themselves, the only high priest we have
now is sitting at the right hand of the
father. and his name is Jesus. Right.
All right.
Hope that answered your question. Sister
Deborah, we going into new territory.
Yes. We are now into tonight's Q&A for
Wednesday, July the 2nd, 2025.
Uh he also says, "Credit account says, I
am 22. I started going to IOG when I was
20 and I have been going over the
thought of getting baptized.
What things should I look at in my walk
to know I am ready?
Well, you want to be on the walk of
making sure that you keeping God's laws,
statutes, and commandments. That's one
of the things. And if you considering
getting baptized, then you have to be
circumcised also. That's number one. But
let's go into Mark 12. Mark the 12th
chapter.
Glad you found us and been walking with
us because we are for real.
Mark 12.
When you get there, let's read that
verse uh 29
and 30. And this is something that Jesus
said to his people. Go ahead.
And Jesus answered him, "The first of
all the commandments is here, O Israel.
The Lord our God is one Lord." Yep.
Listen to the Lord. Go ahead. And thou
shalt love the Lord thy God with all thy
heart and with all thy soul and with all
thy mind and with all thy strength. This
is the first commandment.
Yep. So, if you're at that point too
where that you're ready to serve the
Lord with all your heart and all your
soul and all your mind, you are well on
your way to getting baptized. Turn over
to Acts two. Let's see what Peter said
right quick. Acts two.
When we get there, brother, pick it up
at that verse 38. Let's see what Peter
said here.
Because all have sinned come short of
the glory of God. even you.
Let's go to that uh Acts 2 and pick it
up at 38. Go ahead, brother. Then Peter
said unto them, repent and be baptized
every one of you in the name of Jesus
Christ for the remission of sins, and ye
shall receive the gift of the Holy
Ghost. Yep. So be sorry for whatever
sins have been committed and um continue
to walk with the Lord. Go ahead.
For the promise is unto you and to your
children and to all that are a far off,
even as many as the Lord our God shall
call. Uhhuh. And with many other words
did he testify and exhort, saying, save
yourselves from this unto generation.
Yes, generation definitely untored the
Lord. But read that next verse. Then
what happened? Then they that gladly
received his word were baptized. And the
same day there were added unto them
about 3,000 souls. So if you have
received this word with joy and you feel
in your heart that it is time for you to
get baptized and that is your decision
to make and uh we'll be glad to
accommodate you. That's all I got
and we're going to move on to our next
question. Yes. Stephen Guggis asks, "Is
there a reason why the Lord buried Moses
himself and no one knows where his body
ever was?" Deuteronomy 34 5 and 6 and
Jude 9 is given. All right. Come on,
brother Julius.
Off mute first.
Pardon me. Read that. Tenzel.
Deuteronomy 345 and 6.
Deuteronomy 34 5 and six. So Moses, a
servant of the Lord, died in the land of
Moab according to the word of the Lord.
And he buried him in the valley of the
land of Moab over against Bethor. But no
man knoweth of his septic unto this day.
We can't add to that. The book don't
say, right? The book don't say why.
That's all I got.
All right, we'll leave it right there
with a time check. Next question. Yes,
time is 8:45. We're moving on. Uh
Charles Tumer asks, "If baptized today
in the truth, does that mean
uh slate is clean moving forward?"
If you get baptized, it talks about your
past sins being washed away. But let's
go in that Romans 3. Romans 3.
And let's pick it up at that verse 23.
when you get there and let's see what it
says there. Romans 3 and verse 23.
Go ahead.
For all have sinned and come short of
the glory of God. Uhhuh. Being justified
freely by his grace to the redemption
that is in Christ Jesus. That free gift
we talked about earlier. Go ahead.
whom God have set forth to be a
propitiation through faith in his blood
to declare his righteousness for the
remission of sins that are passed
through the forbearance of God. Yeah. To
declare his righteousness for the
remission of sins that are passed. And
that's part of the baptism. You come out
that water serving God with all your
heart, all your soul, and all your mind.
Hey, them past sins won't even be talked
about long as you stay righteous with
the Lord. But also the thing you have to
remember is then is Hebrews 10. Let's
read that right quick. Hebrews 10 and
two verses. Hebrews 10:26
and 27. Cuz once you get that clean
slate, avoid these two verses right
here. Go ahead, brother. For if we sin
willfully after that we have received
the knowledge of the truth, there remain
of no more sacrifice for sins, but a
certain fearful looking for of judgment
and fiery indignation which shall devour
the adversaries. So you got that clean
slate. Do all you can to keep it clean
and serve God with all your heart and
run this race and run it hard. That's
all I got.
And we're gonna move on to our next
question as time is a ticking. Yes, next
question. P. Smith says, "Can you help
me understand why the mess are referred
to as Russia in the below two text
lessons two mountains of brass 61723
and hour of temptation
23. I'm dealing with two brothers who
are disputing this identification and or
connection.
All right. You got quite a business
question here. Brother Smith guest
caller.
Yeah. Well, the reason they referred to
uh they are the leaders
of the uh uh uh uh of the nation east of
the Euphrates River.
and uh uh and those are the ones that's
going to come against Babylon the great
when the uh uh uh coming up to the wall
of Armageddon
and we going to look at these guys and
see that they come from east of the
Euphr Euphrates River. First, let's go
into Revelation the 9th chapter
and we're going to read verses 13- 16
and then we going to skip Revelation 19
and Revelation the 9th chapter rather
verses 13- 16 9 through uh uh 13- 16
verses 13- 16
and the six angels sounded and I heard a
voice from the four horns of the golden
altar al which is before God, saying to
the six angel which had the trumpet,
loose the four angels which are bound in
the great river Euphrates. And the four
angels were loose which which were
prepared for an hour and a day and a
month and a year for to slay the third
part of men. And the number of the army
of the horsemen were 200,000,000.
And I heard the number of them.
So this is 200 million soldiers and they
gonna come across the Euphrates River.
And that's the Eastern Europe. Get down
and read verse 18.
By these three was the third part of men
killed by the fire and by the smoke and
by the brimstone which issue out of
their mouths.
Now they going to kill a third part of
man. Now let's go into Revelation 16th
chapter and read verses 12- 16.
And the sixth angel poured out his bow
upon the great river Euphrates, and the
waters therew was dried up, that the way
of the kings of the east might be
prepared. And I saw three unclean
spirits.
Hold on. He said, that the way of the
kings of the east might be prepared.
Right. Who's east of uh uh Euphrates
River and which is east of Turkey?
Russia and her allies. Cuz they going to
be reading leading more than one nation.
But it's Russia and her allies. They are
east of the Euphrates River. But keep
reading. What verse? Verse 13.
Mhm. And I saw three unclean spirits
like frogs come out of the mouth of the
dragon, and out of the mouth of the
beast, and out of the mouth of the false
prophet.
For they are the spirits of devils,
working miracles, which go forth unto
the kings of the earth, and of the whole
world, to gather them to the battle of
the of that great day of God Almighty.
The Now go ahead.
Behold, I come as a thief, but blessed
is he that watchth and keepeth his
garment, lest he walk naked, and they
see his shame. And he gathered them
together into a place called in the
Hebrew tongue, Armageddon.
Now, so we know this is when the Lord
come, don't we? That's right. Right. And
when all the and the kings of the east
on the east of Turkey which were
Euphrates River right through and the
leaders of those king of Russia but then
let's go into Isaiah
13th chapter and we're going to read 1-5
first and we going to find out what else
they call Isaiah 13 1-5 and then we're
going to skip. Go ahead. the bird of
Babylon, which Isaiah the son of Amos
did see. Lift ye up a banner upon the
high mountain, and exalt a voice unto
them. Shake the hand that they may go
into the gates of the nobles. I have
commanded my sanctified ones. I have
also called my mighty ones for my anger,
even them that rejoice in my highness.
The noise of a multitude in the
mountains like eyes of a great people. A
tumultous noise of the kingdoms of
nations gathered together. The Lord of
hosts mustered the ho the the host of
the battle. They come from a far country
from the end of heaven, even the Lord
and the weapons of his indignation to
destroy the whole land.
Now the end of the earth, this is
talking about the east. the end. Once
you got out, step out of Russia, which
is east, you done stepped into uh uh
Alaska, which is west. This is Arishia
and her allies. Now, skip down to verse
and read from 16 to 19. And we going to
see who who he's talking about. That's
these kings from the coast that had come
across the the Euphrates River.
that come from the coast of the earth.
That's east
coast of the earth. Go ahead. Their
children also shall be dashed to pieces
before their eyes. Their houses shall be
spent
of Babylon the great European Union we
talking about. And in Western Europe
that's going to be under them. The these
uh uh Eastern nation led by Russia is
going to bash their children. Go ahead
and read. Their houses shall be spoiled
and their wives ravished. Behold, I will
stir up the me against them, which shall
not regard silver. And as for gold, they
shall not delight in it. And their bows
also shall dash the young men to pieces.
They shall have no pity on the fruit of
the womb. Their eyes shall not spare
children.
and Babylon the glory of kingdoms the
beauty of the called deeds excellency
shall be as when God overthrew Sodom
Megum
so now he going to over uh uh stir up
the uh uh uh the what against him said
me didn't right
this is what's coming against Russia
now let's go in was that that at the end
that was that the 19th verse
years old.
Now, let's go into uh uh Jeremiah 51st
chap 50th chapter. Jeremiah the 50th
chapter. We're going to read 8 and 9 and
then we're going to skip down.
Jeremiah 50 verse8
remove out of the midst of Babylon. Go
forth out of the land of the called
deans, and be as the heos before the
flock. For lo, I will raise and cause to
come up against Babylon, and assemble of
great nations from the north country,
and they shall set themselves in array
against her. From this she shall be
taken. Their arrows shall be as of a
mighty expert man, but none shall return
in vain.
Now, when you go east, you go to Russia.
Russia, ain't nobody more eastern than
Russia. And then Russia in Eastern
Europe, ain't nobody more north than
Russia and her allies. So, skip right on
down now to verse uh 41 and read verse
41 and 42.
Behold, a people shall come from the
north, and a great nation, and many
kings shall be praised up from the
coasts of the earth. They shall hold the
bow in the lands. They are cruel and
would not show mercy. Their voice shall
roar like the sea, and they shall ride
upon horses. Everyone put in array like
a man to the battle against thee, oh
daughter of Babylon.
Now this is the northeast
and that is the coast of the earth
eastern coast of the earth coming
against Babylon the great which we call
European Union now that's going to be
running western Europe now let's go to
last place and see what these and give
you again
what this eastern kings in the kingdom
is called Jeremiah 51 and we're going to
read verses 6 through 11 verse. Go
ahead.
Plead out of the midst of Babylon and
deliver every man his soul. Be not cut
off in her iniquity. For this is the
time of the Lord's vengeance. He will
render unto her a recompense.
Babylon have been a golden cup in the
Lord's hand that made all the earth
drunken. The nations have drunken of her
wine. Therefore, the nations are mad.
But Babylon is suddenly fallen and
destroyed. How for her? Take bomb for
her pain. If so be she may be healed.
But we have we would have healed
Babylon, but she is not healed. Forsake
her. And let us go everyone into his own
country. For her judgment reaches unto
heaven, and is lifted up even to the
skies.
So now this is Babylon. Let you know
this story of the Babylon the great sto
because it talks about revelation why
she didn't uh uh this woman that made
the nation drunk with the wine of her
fornication.
So we know exactly who's coming against
Babylon. So skip down to verse and read
verse 27 and 28 and it'll tell you
again. Go ahead.
Set ye up a standard in the land. Blow
the trumpet among the nations. Prepare
the nations against her. Call together
against her the kingdom of Iraq. Many
and ask. Appoint a captain against her.
Cause the horses to come up as the rough
caterpillars. Prepare against her the
nations with the king of the me, the
captains thereof, and all the rulers
thereof, and all the land of his
dominion.
So we should prepare for what? The kings
of the me, didn't they? That's right.
Because the Mes and the Persians have
always been together. And who are they?
They border the border, Iran and Russia.
Now you got other nations over there,
you know, you even got the uh uh Meog
over there, but they're all a part of
that eastern, but they going to be led
by the kings of the me.
The kings of the me now, the modern day
is Russia.
And on that same area, you got Gog and
Mog still come under the banner of
Russia.
And that's according to prophecy. So
these two brothers can believe what they
want. We just doing what the book say.
That's all I got to say. All right. Hope
that answered your question. Just a
couple of more to go. Sister Deborah,
what's the next? All right. The next one
is from Sister Tanisha.
She says,
"Can you please help me understand what
Isaiah 1 vers 13 and 14 is saying?"
Please help it understand, brother
Julius. Let's go there, Tenzil.
Because this is all about the rebellion
of Israel against the God of Israel, and
the Lord don't like rebellion.
Read when you get there, brother.
The vision of Isaiah, the son of Amar,
which he saw concerning Judah and
Jerusalem in the days of Uzziah. Isaiah
Isaiah 1 13 and 14. Isaiah 113:14.
Yep.
Bring no more vain oblations, incest. It
is an abomination unto me. The new moons
and Sabbaths, the callings of
assemblies, I cannot away with. It is an
iniquity, even the solemn meetings.
Uhhuh. Your new moons and your appointed
feasts. My souls hat
trouble unto me. I am weary to bear
them. Continue. And when you spread
forth your hands, I will hide my eyes
from you. Yet when you make many
prayers, I will not hear. Your hands are
full of blood. Because you won't stop
sinning.
So the Lord don't have no regard for
people even his own that continue in
sin. St. John 9:31 he told you we hear
the Lord God of Israel don't hear the
prayer of sinners. Right? So Israel sin
all the stuff that they was doing and
bring them vain oblations which is their
offerings and sacrifices offerings the
Lord would not accept it because they
would not stop sinning. Verse 11 and
then we're done.
For what purpose is the multitude of
your sacrifice unto me? said the Lord. I
am full of the burnt offerings of rams
and the fat of fed beasts. And I delight
not in the blood of bulllocks or of
lambs or of he goats because those
offerings are for sins.
And so when you won't stop sinning, what
difference do you make? Oh, you could
kill every lamb and bull and goat that
you want. It don't make no difference
because you won't stop sinning, right?
This is what you should do. Verse 17,
and this will be it. Go ahead. Learn to
do well. That means stop and repent.
Learn to do well. Go ahead. Seek
judgment.
Relieve the oppressed.
Judge the fatherless. Plead for the
widow. And that verse 16, you don't got
to read it. He would tell you you got to
wash you, make yourself clean yourself
up. That mean you stop and turn and
start doing what thus said the Lord. Now
the Lord said don't be just hearers of
the word but doers because rebellion is
at the sin of witchcraft. And we know
what the Lord and how he feel about
witches. So that's what this whole
scripture is all about. The rebellion of
Israel and the new moons and all
everything that they was doing. The Lord
didn't have no respect for it because
they would not stop sinning. That's all
I got. Right. We We rebel. Well, all
right. We're gonna move on to our next
question.
Next one. Sandra Allen asks, "Would it
be considered a gift of healing if
someone knows which herbs to put
together for illness?"
Open to the panel. Yeah, I think it
would be a blessing for you if some
herbs was put together in order to help
you with whatever your condition might
be. Anybody else?
All right.
All right, let's move on to the next
one.
Uh, one more after that. Uh, read the
Bible daily as concerning Matthew
13:E30.
Is this in the father's kingdom
first resurrection or both? Matthew 13
verse30.
Jerome
mute.
Sorry. Go ahead and read it. Let both
grow together until the harvest. And at
the time of harvest, I will say to the
reapers, "Gather ye together first the
tears, and bind them in bundles to burn
them, but gather the wheat unto my
barn."
Yeah, it's definitely It's not the
father's kingdom. All right. Uh let's go
read that verse 37-41.
Go ahead.
And he answered and said unto them, he
that sweth the good seed is the son of
man. The field is the world. The good
seed are the childrens of the kingdom.
But the tears are the childrens of the
wicked one. The enemy that sow them is
the devil. The harvest is the end of the
world, and the reapers are the angels.
But as therefore the tears are gathered
and burned in the fire, so shall it be
in the end of this world. The Son of Man
shall send forth his angels, and they
shall gather out of his kingdom all
things that offend, and them which do
iniquity, and shall cast them into a
furnace of fire. There shall be welling
and nashing of teeth. Then shall the
righteous shine forth at the sun in the
kingdom of their father. Who have ears
to hear, let him hear. That's good, bro.
And uh you can um tie that with the
Matthews 25
uh
25th chapter and pick it up at 31.
This is not the father's kingdom. Okay.
Matthews 25. Pick it up at 31. Read to
34.
When the Son of man shall come in his
glory, and all the holy angels with him,
then shall he sit upon the throne of his
glory, and before him shall be gathered
all nations. And he shall separate them
one from another, as the shepherd
divideth his sheep from the goats, and
it shall set the sheep on his right
hand, and the goats on the left. Then
shall the king say unto them on his
right hand, Well, come ye, blessed of my
father, inherit the kingdom prepared for
you from the file foundation of the
world. Verse 41,
then shall you say also unto them on the
left hand, depart from me, ye curse,
into everlasting fire prepared for the
devil and his angels. And last verse
verse verse 46. And these shall go away
into everlasting punishment, but the
righteous into life eternal. Yeah,
that's all I got. All right. Thank you
for that. Hope that answered eight
questions as we do a time check.
Yes, the time is 9:08.
9:08. All right. Well, we have ran out
of time and we just want to let it be
known to everybody that we thank you
from all around the world for joining us
this evening. And if you send in a
question and we have a chance to get to
it, we ask you to please don't resubmit
it. Sister Deborah, take it. Put it in
rotation and we'll deal with that
question next week. But until we all
come together again, be safe, be
blessed, ignore that mercy on us all,
and stay prayed up as Brother Tanzel
close us up. Our Father, which art in
heaven, hallowed be thy name. Thy
kingdom come, thy will be done in earth
as it is in heaven. Give us this day our
daily bread, and forgive us of our debts
as we forgive our debtor, and lead us
not into temptation, but deliver us from
evil. For thine is the kingdom, and the
power, and the glory forever. In Jesus
name we pray. Amen. Amen.